Guide to the New Dimensions Media records M1577
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 1: Accession 2008-144
  - Sub-Series 2: Subject files, 2
    - Business (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - California (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - California Association of Nonprofits (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Cancer (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Cartoons (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Cassette resources (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Catholic charities (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Caves/ancient paintings (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Centenarians (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Children (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Christianity (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Circles (Box 106, Folder 12)
    - Citizen diplomats (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - Communication (Box 106, Folder 14)
    - Communities (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - Computers (Box 106, Folder 16)
    - Consciousness studies (Box 106, Folder 17)
    - Constitutional issues (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - Cooperative communities/cohousing (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - Corporate underwriting (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - Couples (Box 106, Folder 21)
    - Course in miracles (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - Creativity (Box 106, Folder 23)
    - Crime (Box 106, Folder 24)
    - Crop circles (Box 106, Folder 25)
    - Crystals (Box 106, Folder 26)
    - Dance (Box 106, Folder 27)
    - Databases (Box 106, Folder 28)
    - Death and dying (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Dentistry (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Desktop publishing (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Dialogue groups (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Dolphins (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Dowsing (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Dream work (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - Drugs and hallucinagens (Box 107, Folder 8)
    - Drumming (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Dyslexia (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Earth centered spirituality (Box 107, Folder 11)
    - Earth circles (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - Earth summit (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - Earthquakes (Box 107, Folder 14)
    - Earthquake - Loma Prieta, October 17, 1989 (Flat-box 108)
    - Ecology (Box 107, Folder 15-16)
    - Economy and economics (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - Education (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Education abstracts (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Elders (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Eleven: eleven 11:11 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Energy alternatives (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Enneagram (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - Environment (Box 109, Folder 7-8)
    - ERA (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - Eroticism (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - Estrogen (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Euthanasia (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - Event managers (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - Exercise (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - Etraterrestrials (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - Eyes (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - Family (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - Feminist issues (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - Feng shui (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - Film resources (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Firewalking (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Flower essences (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Food (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Foreign resources (travel) (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Forestry issues (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - Freedon of press (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Garbage (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - Gardening (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - GATT (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - Genetic engineering (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - Geothermal (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - Global contacts (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - Goddess spirituality (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - Graphic ideas/art (Box 110, Folder 15)
    - Greenhouse effect (Box 110, Folder 16)
    - Gulf War 1991 (Box 110, Folder 17)
    - Handicapped (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - Health (Box 110, Folder 19-20)
    - Health - Chinese herbs (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - Health - eye care (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Health care issues (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Hemp - Kenaf (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Herbs (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Holistic medicine (Box 111, Folder 6)
    - Homeless (Box 111, Folder 7)
    - Homeopathy (Box 111, Folder 8)
    - Horses (Box 111, Folder 9)
    - Hospice (Box 111, Folder 10)
    - Human rights (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - Huna (Box 111, Folder 12)
    - Hypnotherapy (Box 111, Folder 13)
    - Ice Age (Box 111, Folder 14)
    - Indians (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - Indigenous peoples (Box 111, Folder 16)
    - International networking organizations (Box 111, Folder 17)
    - Ireland (Box 111, Folder 18)
    - IRS (Box 111, Folder 19)
    - Islam (Box 111, Folder 20)
    - Japan (Box 111, Folder 21)
    - Jesus (Box 111, Folder 22)
    - Journalism (Box 111, Folder 23)
    - Kabbalah (Box 111, Folder 24)
    - Lady of Guadalupe (Box 111, Folder 25)
    - Law (Box 111, Folder 26)
    - Lesbian and gay issues (Box 111, Folder 27)
    - Life enhancing games/toys (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - Light (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Local resources (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Logging issues (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - LSD and other mind substances (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Macrobiotics (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Magazine rate cards (Box 112, Folder 7-8)
    - Magazine trade outs (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Mailing lists (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Mary Magdalene (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Marijuana (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Martial arts (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Mask making (Box 112, Folder 14)
    - Media groups (Box 112, Folder 15)
    - Massage (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - Menopause (Box 112, Folder 17)
    - Metaphysics (Box 112, Folder 18)
    - Men's issues (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Micro lending/micro finance (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Mexico (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous newsletters (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous resource catalogs (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Mothering (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Multi-cultural (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - Multi-level marketing (Box 113, Folder 8)
    - Music (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - Music therapy (Box 113, Folder 10)
    - Nation of Islam (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - Native Americans (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - Native Americans - local (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - ND translations (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - Near death (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - New Age as a movement (Box 113, Folder 16)
    - New Age humor (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - New Age products (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - New business paradigms (Box 113, Folder 19)
    - New science (Box 114, Folder 1)
    - New technology (Box 114, Folder 2)
    - News media (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - NLP (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Non-profit 501(c)(3) information (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Nuclear disarm (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Nuclear waste (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Open mind (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Oracles (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Organic food (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Our Lady of Gudalupe (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Oxygen (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Paganism (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Past lives (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Peace articles (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Peace groups (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - People of color (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Personnel policies (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Pesticides (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Photo print (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - Poetry (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - Politics/political movements (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - Population (Box 114, Folder 23)
    - Pornography (Box 114, Folder 24)
    - Prenatal research (Box 114, Folder 25)
    - Prisons (Box 114, Folder 26)
    - Printers (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Producer's guide (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Product catalogs (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Prozac (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Psychedelics (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Psychiatric facilities (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Publisher's catalogs (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Racism (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Radio program and producation (Box 115, Folder 9)
      Includes demo cd of Patricia Raskin "Positive Living" and an introductory prsentation cd of A Man's World.
    - Radon (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Railroads (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Rain forest (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Recovered memories (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Recovery and shame (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Recycling (Box 115, Folder 15)
    - Reiki (Box 115, Folder 16)
    - Reincarnation (Box 115, Folder 17)
    - Relationship (Box 115, Folder 18)
    - Religion (Box 115, Folder 19)
    - Religious science (Box 115, Folder 20)
    - Responsible broadcaster (Box 115, Folder 21)
    - Retreat and conference centers (Box 115, Folder 22)
    - Rhythm therapy (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Ritual abuse (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Rivers (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Runes (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Sacred sites (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Science and religion (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Self-esteem groups (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Sexual abuse (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Slide show (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Socially responsible investigating (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Solar technology (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Sound (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Sound studio (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Sounds true (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - South and Central American relations (Box 116, Folder 16)
    - Soviet-American (Box 116, Folder 17)
    - Space travel (Box 116, Folder 18)
    - Spontaneous remission (Box 116, Folder 19)
    - Statistics - miscellaneous (Box 116, Folder 20)
    - South Africa (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Storytelling (Box 116, Folder 21)
    - Student-teacher relationship (Box 116, Folder 22)
    - Systems thinking and cybernetics (Box 116, Folder 23)
    - Sufism (Box 116, Folder 24)
    - T-shirts (Box 116, Folder 25)
    - Tape catalog samples (Box 116, Folder 26)
    - Tape duplicating (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Tax alternatives (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Telemarketing (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Telephone services (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Theater (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Time (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Trainings (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Transpersonal psychology (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Travel (Box 117, Folder 9-10)
    - TV shows (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Tibet (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - U. S. Post Office (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - UFO's (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Ukiah public forum (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Vals - values and lifestyles (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Vegetarianism (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Videos (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Violence (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Volunteers (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Water (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Women (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Work Counselors (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Yoga (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Youth organizations (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Youth project (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - Zapatistas (Box 118, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 3: Organizations, Conferences, etc., 3
    - Chalice Well Trust (Glastonbury) (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Christic Institute (Box 119, Folder 2-3)
    - California Institute of Integral Studies (Box 119, Folder 4-6)
    - California Institute of Integral Studies (Box 120, Folder 1-3)
    - CIAS - California Institute of Asian Studies (Box 120, Folder 4-5)
    - Commonweal (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Compassionate Friends (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Council for a Parliament of the World's Religions (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Cultural Integration Felowship (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Earth Circles Renewal Center (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Elmwood Institute (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Emissary (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Esalen (Box 122, Folder 1-4)
    - EST (Box 123, Folder 1-3)
    - Farallones Institute (Box 123, Folder 4)
    - Fetzer Institute (Box 123, Folder 5)
    - Findhorn Foundation (Box 123, Folder 6)
    - Findhorn Foundation (Box 124, Folder 1-2)
    - F.I.R.E. Firewalking Institute of Research and Education (Box 124, Folder 3)
    - Foundation for Deep Ecology (Box 124, Folder 4)
    - Foundation for New Era Philanthropy (Box 124, Folder 5-6)
    - Foundation for Shamanic Studies (Box 123, Folder 7)
    - Fuller (Buckminster) Institute (Box 121, Folder 8)
    - Fuller (Buckminster) Institute - related projects (Box 124, Folder 9)
    - Gandhi (Box 124, Folder 10)
    - Girafffe Project (Box 124, Folder 11)
    - Global exchange (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Global Exchange (Box 125, Folder 1)
    - Grace Cathedral (Box 125, Folder 2)
    - Graduate Theological Union (Box 125, Folder 3)
    - Green Tradition (Box 125, Folder 4)
    - Green Earth Foundation (Box 125, Folder 5)
    - Greenpeace (Box 125, Folder 6-7)
    - Growing Community (Box 125, Folder 8)
    - Growing Community Newsletter (Box 125, Folder 9)
    - Guild for Psychological Studies (Box 125, Folder 10)
    - HeartMath series (Box 125, Folder 11)
    - Hearts of Space (Box 125, Folder 12)
    - Heifer Project (Box 125, Folder 13)
    - Hoffman Institute (Box 125, Folder 14)
    - Holistic Life Seminars (Box 125, Folder 15)
    - Holistic Life Travels, Holistic Life Foundation (Box 125, Folder 16)
    - Holistic Life University, Holistic Life Institute (Box 126, Folder 1-2)
    - Hollyhock (Box 126, Folder 3)
    - Hope Spring (Box 126, Folder 4)
    - Hopland, City of (Box 126, Folder 5)
    - Hopland Field Station (Box 126, Folder 6)
    - Hunger Project (Box 127, Folder 1-3)
    - IAETF: International Anti-Euthanasia Task Force (Box 127, Folder 4)
    - InnoVision (Box 127, Folder 5)
    - Inside Edge/InnerEdge (Box 127, Folder 6)
    - Inside Ireland (Box 127, Folder 7)
    - Institute for Deep Ecology (Box 127, Folder 8)
    - Institute for Food and Development Policy (Box 127, Folder 9)
    - Institute for Public Accuracy (Box 127, Folder 10)
    - Institute for the Study of Conscious Evolution (Box 127, Folder 11)
    - Institute of Holistic Life (Box 128, Folder 1)
    - Integrities (Box 128, Folder 2)
    - Institute of Noetic Sciences (IONS) (Box 128, Folder 3-7)
    - Institute of Noetic Sciences (IONS) (Box 129, Folder 1-2)
    - Institute of Noetic Sciences (IONS) - Conference 1994 (Box 129, Folder 3)
    - Institute of Noetic Sciences (IONS) - Conference 1996 (Box 129, Folder 4)
    - Institute of Noetic Sciences (IONS) - Conference 1998 (Box 129, Folder 5)
    - Institute of Transpersonal Psychology (Box 129, Folder 6)
    - International Transpersonal Center (Box 129, Folder 7)
    - International Transpersonal Association (ITA) (Box 129, Folder 8)
    - International Transpersonal Association Programs (Box 130, Folder 1)
    - International Transpersonal Association Conference 1994 (Box 130, Folder 2-3)
    - International Transpersonal Association Conference 1995 (Box 130, Folder 4)
    - Internews Report (Box 130, Folder 5)
    - Intuition Magazine (Box 130, Folder 6)
    - Jesus Seminar (Box 130, Folder 7)
    - Joy Lake Community (Box 130, Folder 8)
    - Jungian-Senoi Institute (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - KALW Information Radio (Box 130, Folder 10)
    - K'an Herb Company (Box 131, Folder 1)
    - John F. Kennedy University (Box 131, Folder 2-3)
    - KNOW Communications (Box 131, Folder 4)
    - KQED (Box 131, Folder 5)
    - KFA Krishnamurti Foundation of America (Box 131, Folder 6)
    - Lama Foundation (Box 131, Folder 7)
    - Laughing Coyote Productions (Box 131, Folder 8)
    - Leadership Mendocino (Box 131, Folder 9)
    - League of Conservation Voters (Box 131, Folder 10)
    - The Learning Annex (Box 131, Folder 11)
    - Life Counseling Institute of America (Box 131, Folder 12)
    - LIND: Learning in New Dimensions (Box 131, Folder 13)
    - Living Enrichment Center (Box 132, Folder 1)
    - Love of Wisdom (Box 132, Folder 2)
    - MacArthur Foundation (Box 132, Folder 3)
    - Mann Ranch (Box 132, Folder 4)
    - Meeting of the Ways (Box 132, Folder 5)
    - M.I.A.D. Milwaukee Institute of Art & Design (Box 132, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Communities (Box 132, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous Conferences (Box 132, Folder 8-9)
    - Miscellaneous Death and Dying Organizations (Box 133, Folder 1)
    - Monroe Institute of Applied Sciences (Box 133, Folder 2)
    - Muppets (Box 133, Folder 3)
    - Music for People (Box 133, Folder 4-5)
    - Mystic Fire Video (Box 133, Folder 6)
    - National Federation of Community Broadcasters (NFCB) (Box 133, Folder 7)
    - Natural Law Party (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - Network for Attitudinal Healing International, Inc.: The Heart Connection (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - Network (Box 133, Folder 10)
    - Neuro Linguistic Programming Center (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - New Age Publishing (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - New College of California (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - New Games Foundation (Box 134, Folder 4-5)
    - New Road Map Foundation (Box 134, Folder 6-7)
    - New Society Publishers (Box 135, Folder 1)
    - New World Radio (Box 135, Folder 2)
    - Noarthern California Book Publicity & Marketing Association: NCBPMA (Box 135, Folder 3)
    - Nyingma Institute (Box 135, Folder 4-6)
    - Occidental Arts & Ecology Center (Box 135, Folder 7)
    - The Ojai Foundation (Box 136, Folder 1)
    - ONe Spirit Book Club (Robert Welsch) (Box 136, Folder 2)
    - The Omega Institute for Holistic Studies (Box 136, Folder 3-4)
    - Open Center (Box 136, Folder 5)
    - The Option Institute (Box 136, Folder 6)
    - Orcher of Melchizedek (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Orff Music & Movement (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Original Face Video (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Owner Builder Center (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Pachamama Alliance (Box 137, Folder 3)
    - Pacifica (NFCB) (Box 137, Folder 4)
    - Pacifica Graduate Institute (Box 137, Folder 5)
    - Parabola (Box 137, Folder 6)
    - Parliament of World Religions (Box 137, Folder 7-8)
    - Parliament of World Religions (Box 138, Folder 1-3)
    - Pathways Institute (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - Pathways to Peace (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - PAX Millenia (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Peacenet (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Plowshares (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Pocket Ranch Institute (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Prague, City of (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Process Work - LA (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Process Work - Northern California (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Project Booklift (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Project Vicotry (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Public Conversations Project (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - Public Radio Satellite System (Box 138, Folder 16)
    - Publisher's Weekly articles (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Radio Bilingue (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Radio for Peace Internatinal (RFPI) (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Radiomail Corporation (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Real Goods (Box 139, Folder 5-8)
    - Retreats and Conference Centers (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Right Hand Productions (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Right Livelihood Awards (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Rigoberta (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Rigpa (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Russian River Watershed (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Search for Common Ground (Box 140, Folder 7)
      Includes CD-ROM with organizatonal video and information about the webpage.
    - San Francisco Ecology Center (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Santa Rosa Medical Group (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Santa Sabina Center (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Saybrook Institute (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - Schumacher College (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - E. F. Schumacher Society (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - Science of Mind (Box 140, Folder 14)
    - Scientology (Box 141, Folder 1)
    - The Sedona Method (Training and Associates) (Box 141, Folder 2-3)
    - Seeds of Change (Box 141, Folder 4)
    - Seeing Beyond (Box 141, Folder 5)
    - Seth Network (Box 141, Folder 6)
    - Seva Foundation (Box 141, Folder 7)
    - Betty Shabazz (Box 141, Folder 8)
    - Shaman's Drum (Box 141, Folder 9)
    - Shambhala Publications (Box 141, Folder 10)
    - Shanti Publications (Box 141, Folder 11)
    - Shared Visions (Box 142, Folder 1)
    - Shasta Abbey (Box 142, Folder 2)
    - Shenoa Retreat Center (Box 142, Folder 3)
    - Society for the Advancement of Global Evoklution (SAGE) (Box 142, Folder 4)
    - Space (Box 142, Folder 5)
    - Spirit at Workd (Box 142, Folder 6)
    - Spirit Rock Meditation Center (Box 142, Folder 7)
    - Spiritual Community Guide (Box 142, Folder 8)
    - Spiritual Emergency Network (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - St. George Homes (Box 142, Folder 10)
    - Stanford University Libraries Sound Archive (Box 142, Folder 11)
    - Stanley Foundation (Box 142, Folder 12)
    - Stillpoint Publications (Box 142, Folder 13)
    - Summit University of Louisiana (Box 142, Folder 14)
    - The Sun Magazine (Box 142, Folder 15)
    - Swedenborg Foundation (Box 142, Folder 16)
    - Tarcher, Putnam Publishing (Box 142, Folder 17)
    - Ten Speed Celestial Arts Press (Box 142, Folder 18)
    - Thinking Allowed Productions (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Transitions Bookplace (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Travel Horizons (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Ukiah Chamber of Commerce (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Ukiah, City of (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Unitarian Universalist Association (Box 143, Folder 6)
      Cassette: William F. Schulz, WBZ, Boston, Talk Show promo, December 1986
    - Unity (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Unity and Diversity (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Unity Center (Box 144, Folder 1-2)
    - Universal LIfe Church (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - University for Humanistic Studies (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - University of Peace (World Peace University) (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - University of California Extension - Santa Cruz (Box 144, Folder 6-7)
    - Upaya Zen Center (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Upland HIlls Ecological Awareness Center (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Uranita Brotherhood (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Vedanta Society of Northern California (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Wakan Foundation for the Arts (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Warner Books (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - The West Company (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Westerbeke Ranch (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Who's Who - Strathmore's (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Whole Earth Review (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Wilbur Hot Springs (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Wisdom Circles (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - World Work (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - ZBS Productions (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Zeitguiest Video (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - Zen Hospice Project (Box 145, Folder 15)
    - Zygon International (Box 145, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 4: Release Forms, 4
    - Signed by individuals, alphabetical A - Z; Feltzer; all photocopies (Carton 146)
  - Sub-Series 5: Transcripts, 5
    Written transcripts of aired radio programs of guests interviewed by Michael and/or Justine Toms.
    - Roots for Healing; alphabetical A - D (Box 147)
    - Alphabetical E-M (Box 148)
    - Alphabetical M (continued) - S (Box 149)
    - Alphabetical T-Y; Tape log (Box 150)
  - Sub-Series 6: Newsletters, Program Guides and information about New Dimensions as an organization, 6
    - New Dimensions brochures (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Ads in magazines (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Articles about Michael and Justine Toms (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Newsletters and program guides, 1974-1980 (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Program guides, 1981 (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Program guides, 1982 (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Program guides, 1983 (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Program guides, 1984 (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - New Dimension Radio Network News, 1985 (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - New Dimension Radio Network News, 1986 (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - New Dimension Radio Network News, 1987 (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - New Dimension Radio Network News; The Newsletter of New Dimensions, 1988 (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - The Newsletter of New Dimensions, 1989 (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - The Newsletter of New Dimensions, 1990 (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - The Newsletter of New Dimensions, 1991 (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - The Journal of New Dimensions Radio, 1992 (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - The Journal of New Dimensions Radio, 1993 (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - The Journal of New Dimensions Radio, 1994 (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - The Journal of New Dimensions Radio, 1995 (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - The Journal of New Dimensions Radio, 1996 (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - The Journal of New Dimensions Radio, 1997 (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - The Journal of New Dimensions Radio, 1998 (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - The Journal of New Dimensions Radio, 1999 (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - The Journal of New Dimensions Radio, 2000 (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - New Dimensions Radio Newsletter, 2001 (Half-box 154, Folder 1)
    - New Dimensions Radio Newsletter, 2002 (Half-box 154, Folder 2)